Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Mail Log Files, 1991-1995; I.
  - Secretary of the University, 2.
    - Metalworking Technology Inc. (MTI) - Concurrent Technologies Corporation, 2.21.6.
      - 2.21.6. Metalworking Technology Inc. (MTI) - Concurrent Technologies Corporation, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 15-17)
      - 2.21.6. Metalworking Technology Inc. (MTI) - Concurrent Technologies Corporation, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Mid-Atlantic Technology Application Center (MTAC), 2.21.7.
      - 2.21.7. Mid-Atlantic Technology Application Center (MTAC), 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
      - 2.21.7. Mid-Atlantic Technology Application Center (MTAC), 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
      - 2.21.7. Mid-Atlantic Technology Application Center (MTAC), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - National Environmental Technology Application Corp. (NETAC), 2.21.8.
      - 2.21.8. National Environmental Technology Application Corp. (NETAC), 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Technology Center - J&L Site, 2.21.9
      - 2.21.9. Pittsburgh Technology Center - Jones & Laughlin Site, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Trustee Assignments, 2.22.
      - 2.22. Trustee Assignments, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - 2.22. Trustee Assignments, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - 2.22. Trustee Assignments, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 3.
    The 3.0 Mail Log files deal specifically with the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, as well as most student activities. This includes those records relating to student organizations and activities such as homecoming, the Pitt News, fraternities and sororities, and the Student Government Board. The records include correspondence, some event plans, and program information.
    - Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 3.0.
      - 704.00. Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - 3.0. Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - 3.0. Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
      - 3.0. Office of the Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Counseling and Student Development, 3.2.
      - 3.2. Counseling and Student Development, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Placement Service, 3.3.
      - 704.03. Placement Service, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - 3.3. Placement Service, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - 3.3. Placement Service, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - 3.3. Placement Service, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - International Student Services, 3.4.
      - 3.4. International Student Services, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - 3.4. International Student Services, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - 3.4. International Student Services, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Student Activities, 3.5.
      - 704.04. Housing and Food Services, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - 3.5. Student Activities, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - 3.5. Student Activities, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - 3.5. Student Activities, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Homecoming, 3.5.1.
      - 3.5.1. Homecoming, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - 3.5.1. Homecoming, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - 3.5.1. Homecoming, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Fraternities and Sororities, 3.6.
      - 704.05A. Fraternities and Sororities, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - 3.6. Fraternities and Sororities, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - 3.6. Fraternities and Sororities, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - 3.6. Fraternities and Sororities, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Student Government, 3.7.
      - 704.05B. Student Government, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - 3.7. Student Government, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - 3.7. Student Government, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - 3.7. Student Government, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Student Organizations, 3.9.
      - 3.9. Student Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - 3.9. Student Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - 3.9. Student Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Pitt News, 3.10.
      - 3.10. Pitt News, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Facilitating Opportunity and Climate for Underrepresented Students (FOCUS), 3.11.
      - 3.11. Facilitating Opportunity and Climate for Underrepresented Students (FOCUS), 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - 3.11. Facilitating Opportunity and Climate for Underrepresented Students (FOCUS), 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Student Health Services Review Committee, 3.12.
      - 3.12. Student Health Services Review Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 4.
    Material in the 4.0 Mail Log files pertains to the activities of the Office for Institutional Advancement. It includes information on major grant awards sought and received by the university, particularly through the grant reports and acknowledgement letters from Chancellor O'Connor in 04.06.06. Major foundations that the university consistently interacted with, such as the Hillman Foundation, have their own individual files. These records also include material relating to alumni, such as correspondence with and regarding the Alumni Association and major events on the university's calendar, such as Honors Convocation and Commencement. It also covers the Office of Special Events and the various programming efforts established by that office. The bulk of the material for events listed after 4.9 consists of guest lists.
    - Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 4.0.
      - 600.00. Vice President, University Relations and Development, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - 4.0. Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
      - 4.0. Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 6-11)
      - 4.0. Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
      - 4.0. Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      - 4.0. Vice Chancellor for Institutional Advancement, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Annual Giving Fund (AGF) and Pitt's Internal Campaign (PIC), 4.1.
      - 602.01. Annual Giving Fund (AGF) and Pitt's Internal Campaign (PIC), 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - 4.1. Annual Giving Fund (AGF) and Pitt's Internal Campaign (PIC), 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - 4.1. Annual Giving Fund (AGF) and Pitt's Internal Campaign (PIC), 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - United Way, 4.2.
      - 602.02. United Way, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - 4.2. United Way, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - 4.2. United Way, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - 4.2. United Way, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Development Proposals, 4.3.
      - 600.00E. Development Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - 4.3. Development Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - 4.3. Development Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - 4.3. Development Proposals, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - 4.3. Development Proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Pitt Ambassadors, 4.4.
      - 600.00C. Pitt Ambassadors, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - 4.4. Pitt Ambassadors, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - 4.4. Pitt Ambassadors, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - 4.4. Pitt Ambassadors, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Inaugural Invitations (Outside University), 4.5.
      - 602.00B. Inaugural Invitations (Outside University), 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - 4.5. Inaugural Invitations (Outside University), 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - 4.5. Inaugural Invitations (Outside University), 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Gifts and Grants, 4.6.
      - 4.6. Gifts and Grants, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - 4.6. Gifts and Grants, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
      - 4.6. Gifts and Grants, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Alcoa Foundation, 4.6.1.
      - 604.03G. Alcoa Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - 4.6.1. Alcoa Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - 4.6.1. Alcoa Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - 4.6.1. Alcoa Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Awards, 4.6.2.
      - 604.02. Awards, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - 4.6.2. Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - 4.6.2. Awards, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - 4.6.2. Awards, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Buhl Foundation, 4.6.3.
      - 4.6.3. Buhl Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - 4.6.3. Buhl Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Exxon Education Foundation, 4.6.4.
      - 604.03E. Exxon Education Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - 4.6.4. Exxon Education Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 4.6.4. Exxon Education Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 4.6.4. Exxon Education Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships, 4.6.5.
      - 604.05. Fellowships, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - 4.6.5. Fellowships, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - 4.6.5. Fellowships, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - 4.6.5. Fellowships, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 4.6.6.
      - 604.02. Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 12-15)
      - 4.6.6. Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
      - 4.6.6. Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 18-20)
      - 4.6.6. Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 21-22)
      - 4.6.6. Gifts and Grants over $5,000, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Heinz, 4.6.8.
      - 604.03D. Heinz, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - 4.6.8. Heinz, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - 4.6.8. Heinz, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - 4.6.8. Heinz, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
      - 4.6.7. Heinz, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Vira Heinz Endowment, 4.6.9.
      - 604.03I. Vira Heinz Endowment, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - 4.6.9. Vira Heinz Endowment, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - 4.6.9. Vira Heinz Endowment, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - 4.6.9. Vira Heinz Endowment, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Hillman Foundation, 4.6.10.
      - 604.03A. Hillman Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - 4.6.10. Hillman Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - 4.6.10. Hillman Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - 4.6.10. Hillman Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Lilly Foundation, 4.6.11.
      - 604.03K. Lilly Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - 4.6.11. Lilly Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - 4.6.11. Lilly Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - The Pittsburgh Foundation, 4.6.12.
      - 604.03J. The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - 4.6.12. The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - 4.6.12. The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - 4.6.12. The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - 4.6.12. The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - R. K. Mellon and A. W. Mellon Foundations, 4.6.14.
      - 604.03B. R. K. Mellon and A. W. Mellon Foundations, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - 4.6.14. R. K. Mellon and A. W. Mellon Foundations, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - 4.6.14. R. K. Mellon and A. W. Mellon Foundations, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 604.03C.
      - 604.03C. Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Shell Oil Co. Foundation, 604.03L.
      - 604.03L. Shell Oil Co. Foundation, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Alumni Association, 4.7.
      - 602.00. Alumni Association, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - 4.7. Alumni Association, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
      - 4.7. Alumni Association, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - 4.7. Alumni Association, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 4.7. Alumni Association, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - William Pitt Forum, 600.00B.
      - 600.00B. William Pitt Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Campaign for the Third Century, 602.00A.
      - 602.00A. Campaign for the Third Century, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - University Relations, 4.8.
      - 601.00. University Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - 4.8. University Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - 4.8. University Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
      - 4.8. University Relations, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
    - Communications Board of Visitors, 4.8.1.
      - 4.8.1. Communications Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Pitt Press Releases and Announcements, 4.8.2.
      - 601.02. Pitt Press Releases and Announcements, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - 4.8.2. Pitt Press Releases and Announcements, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - 4.8.2. Pitt Press Releases and Announcements, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - 4.8.2. Pitt Press Releases and Announcements, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - University Times, 4.8.3.
      - 4.8.3. University Times, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - 4.8.3. University Times, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - 4.8.3. University Times, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Special Events, 4.9.
      - 4.9. Special Events, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - 4.9. Special Events, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
      - 4.9. Special Events, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
    - Honors Convocation, 4.9.0.
      - 603.10. Honors Convocation, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - 4.9.0. Honors Convocation, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - 4.9.0. Honors Convocation, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - 4.9.0. Honors Convocation, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - 4.9.0. Honors Convocation, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - American Experience Lectures and Dinners, 4.9.2.
      - 4.9.2. American Experience Lectures and Dinners, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - 4.9.2. American Experience Lectures and Dinners, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Chancellor's Band Concert, 4.9.3.
      - 603.27. Chancellor's Band Concert, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - 4.9.3. Chancellor's Band Concert, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - 4.9.3. Chancellor's Band Concert, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - 4.9.3. Chancellor's Band Concert, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, 4.9.4.
      - 603.01. Commencement, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - 4.9.4. Commencement, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - 4.9.4. Commencement, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - 4.9.4. Commencement, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Cookout for Student Leaders, 4.9.5.
      - 4.9.5. Cookout for Student Leaders, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - 4.9.5. Cookout for Student Leaders, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Distinguished Faculty Reception, 4.9.6.
      - 4.9.6. Distinguished Faculty Reception, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - 4.9.6. Distinguished Faculty Reception, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - 4.9.6. Distinguished Faculty Reception, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Heinz Distinguished Lecture, 4.9.7.
      - 603.07. Heinz Distinguished Lecture, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Lantern Night Ceremony, 4.9.8.
      - 603.18. Lantern Night Ceremony, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - 4.9.8. Lantern Night Ceremony, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - 4.9.8. Lantern Night Ceremony, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - 4.9.8. Lantern Night Ceremony, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Music for the Christmas Season, 4.9.9.
      - 603.20. Music for the Christmas Season, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - 4.9.9. Music for the Christmas Season, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - 4.9.9. Music for the Christmas Season, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - 4.9.9. Music for the Christmas Season, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - New Faculty Orientation, 4.9.10.
      - 603.02. New Faculty Orientation, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - 4.9.10. New Faculty Orientation, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - 4.9.10. New Faculty Orientation, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - 4.9.10. New Faculty Orientation, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Picnic for New Students, 4.9.11.
      - 4.9.11. Picnic for New Students, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - 4.9.11. Picnic for New Students, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Reception for Faculty and Staff Who Have Published, 4.9.13.
      - 4.9.13. Reception for Faculty and Staff Who Have Published, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Reception for Mentors, 4.9.14.
      - 4.9.14. Reception for Mentors, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Reception for Scholars, 4.9.15.
      - 4.9.15. Reception for Scholars, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - 4.9.15. Reception for Scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Reception for New Students from Abroad, 4.9.16.
      - 4.9.16. Reception for New Students from Abroad, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - 4.9.16. Reception for New Students from Abroad, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Senate Council Receptions, 4.9.18.
      - 4.9.18. Senate Council Receptions, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - 4.9.18. Senate Council Receptions, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Trustees' Dinner, 4.9.19.
      - 4.9.19. Trustees' Dinner, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Presidential Installation, 603.05.
      - 603.05. Presidential Installation, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 40-41)
    - Heinz Chapel, 4.10.
      - 605.00. Heinz Chapel, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - 4.10. Heinz Chapel, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - 4.10. Heinz Chapel, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - 4.10. Heinz Chapel, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Nationality Rooms, 4.11.
      - 607.00. Nationality Rooms, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - 4.11. Nationality Rooms, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - 4.11. Nationality Rooms, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 48)
      - 4.11. Nationality Rooms, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Stephen Foster Memorial, 4.12.
      - 4.12. Stephen Foster Memorial, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - 4.12. Stephen Foster Memorial, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 51)
      - 4.12. Stephen Foster Memorial, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 52)
      - 4.12. Stephen Foster Memorial, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Department of Athletics, 5.
    The files in the 5.0 Mail Log focus on the Department of Athletics at the University of Pittsburgh. This includes information on planning football game events, discussion of Pitt Stadium issues and potential fundraising, correspondence with the Athletic Director and head coaches, and more. The Pitt Band is also periodically represented in records here. Material in Mail Log 5.12 has been restricted and requires a signed confidentiality agreement.
    - Department of Athletics, 5.0.
      - 706.00. Department of Athletics, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 54)
      - 5.0. Department of Athletics, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 55)
      - 5.0. Department of Athletics, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 56-58)
      - 5.0. Department of Athletics, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
      - 5.0. Department of Athletics, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Big East Conference, 5.2.
      - 706.10. Big East Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - 5.2. Big East Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - 5.2. Big East Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - 5.2. Big East Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
    - College Football Association (CFA), 5.3.
      - 5.3. College Football Association (CFA), 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - 5.3. College Football Association (CFA), 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
      - 5.3. College Football Association (CFA), 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - 5.3. College Football Association (CFA), 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 5.4.
      - 706.07. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - 5.4. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - 5.4. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 16-18)
      - 5.4. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - 5.4. NCAA Special Committee Report, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
      - 5.4. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 6-8)
      - 5.4. National Collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA), 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - NCAA Compliance, 5.4.1.
      - 5.4.1. NCAA Compliance, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - 5.4.1. NCAA Compliance, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 11-12)
      - 5.4.1. NCAA Compliance, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Football, 5.5.
      - 5.5. Football, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - 5.5. Football, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - 5.5. Football, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Football Games, 1992-1993; 5.5.1992.
      - 5.5.1. Pitt vs. Kent State, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - 5.5.2. Pitt vs. West Virginia, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - 5.5.4. Pitt vs. Minnesota, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - 5.5.6. Pitt vs. Notre Dame, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - 5.5.8. Pitt vs. East Carolina, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - 5.5.11. Pitt vs. Louisville, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Football Games, 1992-1994; 5.5.1993.
      - 5.5.1. Pitt vs. Southern Mississippi, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - 5.5.2. Pitt vs. Virginia Tech, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - 5.5.3. Pitt vs. Ohio State, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - 5.5.4. Pitt vs. Louisville, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - 5.5.5. Pitt vs. Notre Dame, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - 5.5.6. Pitt vs. Syracuse, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - 5.5.7. Pitt vs. West Virginia, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - 5.5.8. Pitt vs. Rutgers, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - 5.5.9. Pitt vs. Miami, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - 5.5.10. Pitt vs. Boston College, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Football Games, 1994-1995; 5.5.1994.
      - 5.5.1. Pitt vs. Ohio University, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - 5.5.2. Pitt vs. Ohio State, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - 5.5.3. Pitt vs. Boston College, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - 5.5.4. Pitt vs. Louisville, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - 5.5.5. Pitt vs. Syracuse, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - 5.5.6. Pitt vs. West Virginia, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - 5.5.8. Pitt vs. Temple, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - 5.5.10. Pitt vs. Rutgers, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Men's Basketball, 5.6.
      - 706.02A. Men's Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - 5.6. Men's Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - 5.6. Men's Basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - 5.6. Men's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Convocation Center Space Design Committee, 5.6.1.
      - 5.6.1. Convocation Center Space Design Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - 5.6.1. Convocation Center Space Design Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Men's Varsity Sports, 5.7.
      - 5.7. Men's Varsity Sports, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - 5.7. Men's Varsity Sports, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Women's Varsity Sports, 5.8.
      - 5.8. Women's Varsity Sports, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - 5.8. Women's Varsity Sports, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Varsity Letter Club, 5.9.
      - 5.9. Varsity Letter Club, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - 5.9. Varsity Letter Club, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - 5.9. Varsity Letter Club, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 24)